老友记 第六季 第十六集
亲爱的
So, honey, this, uh...
关于玩3P的事
This threesome thing? Uh, heh.
你要去哪里找...
How are we even gonna find...?
我把可能有兴趣的女人 列了出来
Actually, I'm making a list of women I know who might be into this.
哦 哇
Oh. Wow.
嗯哼
Huh.
天哪
Boy.
有人很用功喔
Well, someone's been doing their homework.
是啊 我知道我列了两次盖儿罗斯坦
Yeah. Oh, and I know Gail Rosten is in there twice...
但是她好...
but she is so...
我知道
Oh, I know. Ha, ha.
光是用讲的就让我有点...
You know, just talking about it is getting me kind of...
- 我也是   - 是吗？
- I know. Me too.     - Yeah?
我想班已经睡了
I think Ben's asleep.
哦 嗯...
Oh, um...
我觉得我们最好储存精力
You know, I think it'll be better if we just save it.
也对
Yeah. Heh.
储存精力 没问题
Right. Save it. I can do that.
（贝丝以色列医疗中心）
- 嘿 菲比   - 嘿
- Hey, Pheebs.     -Hey.
嘿 还好吗？
How's it going?
我得离开这张床 我快疯掉了
I've got to get out of this bed. I'm going crazy here! Crazy!
喝吧 甜
Here you go, sweetie.
这是什么？花草茶？我讨厌花草茶
What the hell is this, herbal tea? I hate herbal tea.
- 但是我加了峰蜜   - 不要蜂蜜
- I put some honey in it.     - Nyeh nyeh honey nyeh nyeh.
- 她还不知道她被开除了对吧？ - 对 医生说她会没命
- She doesn't know she was fired?     - No, the doctors say it may kill her.
你们两个女生在窃窃私语什么？
What are you two girls whispering about over there?
不过我觉得应该告诉她
But I think we should tell her.
它好逼真喔
Ugh, I mean, it's just so realistic.
就是啊
I know. Yeah.
- 他的名字叫拍拍   - 拍拍狗
- His name's Pat.     - Pat the dog.
喔...我懂了
Oh! Oh! I get it! Ha, ha!
喔 天啊
Oh, God.
你...
You, uh? You...
- 要续杯了吗？ - 哦 我不该再喝了
- ready for a refill?     - Oh, I probably shouldn't.
- 哦   - 所以我要喝
- Oh.     - So I will! Ha.
哦
Oh!
哇
Wow.
- 感觉好像下雨喔   - 很酷吧？
- It's like it's raining.     - Pretty cool, huh?
要是你以为把鱼扔进去 不会卡进机器里
But if you think a fish wouldn't get sucked into the mechanism...
那你就错了
well, you'd be wrong.
可以借用洗手间吗？
Um, can I use your bathroom?
- 就在那里面   - 好的
- It's, uh, right through there.     - Okay. Ah.
我告诉你
You know, I gotta tell you.
要是一个星期前有人对我说
If someone told me a week ago...
我会在乔伊崔比亚尼家撒尿...
that I would be peeing in Joey Tribbiani's apartment...
人生真美好对吧？
Life's pretty great, isn't it?
希望你饿了
I hope you're hungry.
我们先吃生蚝
We're starting with oysters.
你知道生蚝的作用吧？
You know what they say about oysters, don't you?
它有寄生虫？
They have parasites?
不是
No. Ha, ha.
有人说生蚝是一种春药
Um, well, some people say that oysters are an aphrodisiac.
- 什么人说的？ - 就是人嘛
- What people?     - People.
有人说的
People say it.
过来
Come here.
- 生蚝是吧？ - 哈哈哈
- So, oysters, huh?     - Ha-ha-ha.
然后再吃一些中东的库司库司
And then we're gonna have a little Middle Eastern couscous.
我们可以
Something we can eat...
用手拿着吃
with our hands.
有意思 我们学到传染病时...
When we were studying communicable diseases...
不是...
No, no, no.
这样才性感
It's sensual.
- 我都不知道 好   - 好
- Oh. Didn't know. Okay.     - Okay.
喔 讨厌
Oh, no!
抱歉 医院找我
I'm sorry, it's the hospital.
菜都很棒 帮我留一点？
The food looks great. Save me some?
我可不敢保证
I can't promise anything.
我们是来真的对吧？
We're really gonna do this, huh?
看样子是
Looks like it.
要是你觉得很怪 我们还是可以随时喊停...
If this is too weird for you, you can still back out...
- 我来开   - 好
- I got it!     - Okay.
- 苏珊 嗨   - 嘿
- Susan, hi.     - Hey.
- 谢谢你的加入   - 我怎么可能错过
- Thank you so much for coming.     - I wouldn't have missed it for the world.
我是罗斯
I'm Ross, by the way.
罗斯你好
Hello, Ross.
- 我喜欢你家的布置   - 谢谢你
- I love what you've done with this space.     - Thank you so much. Heh.
好火辣呀
How hot is this?
可惜在这里的是我不是罗杰
I'm sorry you're here with me instead of Roger.
就是啊
Yeah, me too.
我可以让你感到他的存在
Well, I could make it seem like he's here.
关于库司库司的小常识
"Here's some little-known facts about couscous:
第二个库司 是1979年才加的
They didn't add the second 'cous' until 1979."
- 别闹了 一点也不好笑   - 好
- Stop it! That's not funny!     - Okay.
对不起
I'm sorry, okay? It's just...
今晚原本应该很重要的
tonight was supposed to be, you know, a big deal.
- 今晚要干嘛？ - 你不会想知道的
- What was tonight?     - You don't want to know what tonight was.
好吧
Okay.
今晚要干嘛？
What was tonight?
今晚本来是我的初夜
Tonight was going to be my first time.
跟罗杰？
With Roger?
不只是跟罗杰？我的天哪
Not just with Roger? Oh, my God.
别激动 只做过四次的先生
All right, relax, Mr. I've-Had-Sex-Four-Times!
是四个不同的女人
Four different women!
次数就多太多了
I've had sex way more times.
几次？
How many?
九次
Nine.
我只是在等完美的对象
I'm just waiting for the perfect guy.
这样很好啊 你真的觉得罗杰是那个人？
Well, good. Good for you. You really think Roger's the perfect guy?
不是 但他也不算糟
No, but he's not a horrible guy.
我都那样自我介绍
That's what I tell girls about me.
钱德 我会死于处女之身
Chandler, I'm gonna die a virgin!
你不会 你很好很棒
No, you're not. You are sweet and wonderful...
你一定会得到经验
and this is gonna happen for you.
是吗？什么时候？你想跟我做吗？
Oh, really? When? Do you want to do it with me?
好啊
Okay.
我是开玩笑的
I was kidding.
我也是
So was I.
乔伊
Joey.
你真是个了不起的演员
You're such an amazing actor.
你怎么分辨雷莫瑞医生
How do you know where Dr. Drake Ramoray leaves off...
跟乔伊崔比亚尼的转换？
and Joey Tribbiani begins?
雷莫瑞医生有
Well, with Dr. Drake...
现成的台词可说
they always tell me what to say.
乔伊就得自己办了
And with Joey, I pretty much have to make it up on my own.
- 哇   - 嗯
- Wow.     - Mm.
你告诉我...
Tell me something. Whoa!
- 我刚刚从沙发上摔下来   - 没错
- I just fell right off the couch there.     - Yeah, you did.
我没事
I'm okay.
- 坐好 我问你件事   - 好
- Here you go. Let me ask you a question.     - Whoops. Yeah.
上次
When was the last time...
有人称赞你很美丽是什么时候？
someone told you just how beautiful you are?
哇
Wow.
我的手麻了
I can't feel my hands.
手给我
Come on. Come here.
- 嗯哼？ - 嗯哼
- Huh?     - Huh.
- 哦？ - 噢
- Oh?     - Ooh.
- 我们不能这么做   - 没错
- We can't do this.     - No!
- 吃生蚝？ - 好
- Oyster?     - Yeah.
要是我们做了 我压力会很大
If... lf! If we did do this, there'd be a lot of pressure on me.
因为你等了很久 我不想让你失望
Because you've waited a long time, and I wouldn't want to disappoint you.
但是我没得比较
But I have nothing to compare it to.
就算你很逊 我哪会知道？
So even if you were horrible, how would I know?
这个好耶
I do like that.
我还比较累 我得跟另外四个女人比
It's harder for me. I have four women to compete with.
其实只有三个
Well, if it helps, there were only three.
所以只有今晚对吧？
So it'd just be for tonight?
没错 只是朋友在帮朋友的忙
Absolutely. It would just be one friend helping out another friend.
别说了 不行
Stop it. We're not doing this.
- 来做吧   - 不行
- Let's do it!     - No!
- 好吧   - 好吧
- Okay!     - Okay!
那...
So, um...
你有特定的撇步吗？
Do you have any, uh, moves?
我有一些啦
I have some moves.
- 我没有   - 好
- I have no moves.     - Okay.
你在干什么？
Oh, okay, what you doing there?
- 对不起 真的太奇怪了   - 是啊 还是算了
- I'm sorry, this is just too weird.     - Yeah, forget it.
- 要是我关灯呢？ - 好
- What if I turn out the lights?     - Okay.
赞
Oh, yeah.
- 钱德？ - 怎样？
- Chandler?     - Yeah?
那是沙发
That's the couch.
我的老天爷啊
Oh, my God!
就是啊
I know!
告诉你
I'll tell you something.
我们一定要再来一次
We are gonna do that again!
- 没问题   - 啊
- Oh, okay!     - Ah!
早安
Morning.
- 对喔   - 没错
- Oh, right.     - Yeah.
天哪
Oh, God.
居然让乔伊崔比亚尼 听到我吐
Oh, I can't believe Joey Tribbiani heard me throw up.
其实他也看到了点
He actually saw you a little bit too.
不会吧
No.
天哪 我们没有...没有...
Oh, God, we... We didn't, uh?
没有
No. No, no.
看完就没兴致了
Not after seeing that.
天啊 我真是很糟糕
God, I'm just a horrible person.
- 为什么？ - 因为我已经结婚了
- Well, why?     - Because I'm married.
没错 我是有夫之妇
That's right, I'm a married woman.
还跑到一个电视明星家搞外遇
I came to a TV star's apartment to have an affair. Ugh!
别傻了
That's ridiculous.
我才不是明星
I'm not a "star."
只是一般的名演员
I'm just a regular famous actor.
而我是个很糟糕的人
And I'm a horrible, horrible person.
瑞秋 你别再自责了
Rachel, will you stop saying that?
嗨 嗨 听着
Hey. Hey, look.
你记不记得在节目中 卡普丽临死前
Remember on the show when Capri was dying?
- 给了我...   - 石洞里的戒指 记得
- And she gave me...     - The ring from the cave. Yeah.
哇
Wow.
好...
Uh, okay, well...
嗯...
Uh...
天哪 你可以留着它？
Oh, my God! They let you keep that stuff?
当然 只要不被发现 想留什么都行
Sure. As long as they don't find out, you can keep whatever you want.
我要把它送给你
And I want you to have it.
- 不要...   - 要
- No, I couldn't.     - Yes. Yes.
你每次看到它
And every time you look at it...
就要想起你是个好人
I want you to remember that you are a good person.
你有机会外遇
Now, you had the chance to cheat...
而且还是跟我
and with me.
但是你没有 这就是这枚戒指的意义
But you didn't. And that's what this ring stands for.
我以为它是代表 卡普丽对哥哥永不止息的爱
But I thought that ring stood for Capri's undying love for her brother.
- 你到底要不要？ - 我要
- Look, you want the ring or not?     - Yeah!
嘿 看看你 你醒了
Hey, look at you! You're up!
- 太好了   - 我想去走一走
- All right.     - I thought I'd try to take a walk.
你们帮我倒杯水 我马上回来
You pour me some water. I'll be back soon.
你不是想打公共电话回公司吧
Whoa, whoa. You're not gonna call work, are you?
不是 我已经学到教训了
No. I've learned my lesson.
快点 动作快
Let's go. Come on. Move it.
菲比 快
Phoebe, come on!
鞋子 公事包 谢了 祝你的胆囊早日康复
Shoes, briefcase. Thanks, Lou. Good luck with the gallbladder.
乔伊
Hey, Joe...
你...你玩过3P吗？
did you ever have a threesome?
罗斯 我觉得卡萝很漂亮 我也相信你很有魅力 但是...
Look, Ross. Carol's great, and I'm sure you're a very attractive man, but...
不 我...
No, I...
不是 我之所以问你是因为...
No. The reason I'm asking is that...
我昨晚玩了3P
I sort of had one last night.
- 你？ - 对
- You?     - Yeah.
- 哇 好棒  - 是啊
- Wow. All right.     - Yeah.
漂亮 过瘾吗？
So? Was it amazing?
还...
It was, heh...
还好啦
okay.
只有还好？你的玩法对吗？
Just okay? Did you do it right?
你有没有在参加派对时觉得
Look, it's just, did you ever go to a party and think:
"少了我会有什么差别吗？"
"Would anyone really miss me if I weren't here?"
嗯哼
Huh.
不过罗斯
But still, Ross.
跟两个女人玩得再难玩 也胜过其他日子
Your worst day with two women, pretty much better than any other day.
哦 当然
Oh, oh, no, absolutely.
- 你懂吧？ - 那当然
- Yeah.     - Yeah.
只是
It's just...
我这个部分很快就结束了
my part seemed to be over pretty quickly...
然后我就一直等
and then there was a lot of waiting around.
哦
Oh.
你两个都有做到吧？
But you got to be with both of them, right?
没有
Not really.
我只有跟卡萝做
Eh, just Carol.
- 另一个没有？ - 没有 她直把我踹开
- Not the other one?     - No, she kept kicking me away.
- 那样很讨厌   - 就是啊
- You don't want that.     - No.
至少你开了眼界
Hey, at least you got to see a lot of stuff.
是大大的开了眼界
Oh, I saw a lot of stuff.
- 你后来有点无聊？ - 有点
- You get a little bored?     - A little.
- 我弄了点吃的   - 是吗？
- Yeah. Made a snack.     - Yeah?
- 你弄了什么？ - 就是三明治
- What'd you have?     - Just a sandwich.
火鸡肉 加一点芥末酱
Turkey. A little mustard.
- 好像很赞   - 是很赞
- Sounds good.     - It really was.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
跟你说 我昨晚跟一个女生到达本垒了
Let me tell you about this chick I scored with last night.
- 等等 就是你嘛   - 嗯哼
- Oh, no, wait a minute, that was you.     - Heh.
你看我 我是个堕落的女人
Hey, check me out. I'm a slut!
晚上要不要找事情做？
So you, uh, want to do something tonight?
不行 罗杰医生又要来了
Oh, I can't. Dr. Roger's coming over again.
也对
Oh. Oh, right.
因为你还在跟他交往 他人很好
Right. Because you're still seeing him, and, uh, he's a good guy.
我记得有一次...
I remember a time...
- 你还好吧？ - 好得很
- Are you okay?     - Yeah, totally.
你呢？
Totally. Are you?
棒呆了 真的好神奇
Great. It's so amazing.
上次罗杰来的时候我好紧张
Last time Dr. Roger came over, I was so nervous.
但是跟你做过之后 我变成 "医生可以看我了吗？"
But after being with you, I'm like, "Can the doctor see me now?"
一定可以
I'll bet he can.
"我没有预约 但是我需要体检"哈哈
"I don't have an appointment, but I sure could use a physical." Ha, ha.
- 你真的没事？ - 没事 别管我 我很好
- You sure you're okay?     - Don't worry about me, I'll be fine.
啊
Aah!
天哪 巴瑞
My God! Barry!
- 你说你周末都不在   - 哦
- You said you'd be away all weekend!     - Oh!
没错 对不起 我回来早了
That's right, I'm sorry. I am early!
你们请继续
Finish, please!
惊喜 看看谁回来了
Surprise, look who's back.
- 嘿 菲比   - 嘿
- Hey, Pheebs.     - Hey.
通知警卫
Call security.
菲比 你不是被开除了吗？
Pheebs, uh, didn't you get fired?
我可不这么认为
Heh, I don't think so.
- 菲比？ - 杰克 嘿
- Phoebe?     - Jack! Hey. Ha, ha.
- 你来干什么？ - 我好多了 回来上班
- What are you doing here?     - All better. Back to work.
但这个研究部猪头说我被开除了
This clown from research told me I was fired.
他应该用功一点
He should do his research, huh? Ha-ha-ha.
你是被开除了
Well, you were fired.
没有
Nuh-uh.
我跟帮你接电话的人说了
I told that guy who answered your phone.
喔 我没收到留言 所以不算
Oh, okay. I didn't get that message. So this doesn't count.
- 我先进办公室了   - 嗯哼
- Anyway, I'll be in my office.     - Ah, heh.
菲比 你没有办公室了
Phoebe, you don't have an office.
没关系 我在这里工作
All right, I'll work right here.
这里很好 旁边有植物
This is good. Next to this plant.
- 菲比   - 你闯入我的办公室了
- Phoebe, let's...     - You're in my office.
我替这家公司赚了很多钱 而且是大钱
Look, I've made a lot of cash for this company. I am talking big bucks!
比索 日圆 卢布 我才犯了一个小错...
Pesos! Yen! Rubles! You make one little mistake...
你损失了1千3百万元
You lost 13 million dollars.
原来一切都是为了钱
So now this is all about money?
我已经够...
You know, it's bad enough that... Ow!
别闹了吧
Oh, you have got to be kidding.
- 你还好吗？ - 我心脏病又发作了
- Are you all right?     - I'm having another heart attack.
- 什么？ - 我的心脏病又发作了
- What?     - I'm having another heart attack!
叫救护车
Call 911!
猪头
Dumb-ass!
菲比 你好吗？
Pheebs, how's it going?
我被开除 心脏病发作
They fired me, and I'm having a heart attack.
- 欢迎归队   - 好
- Well, welcome back.     - Yeah.
- 嗨 罗斯   - 嗨 瑞秋
- Hi, Ross.     - Hi, Rachel.
- 乔伊崔比亚尼在吗？ - 不在
- Is Joey Tribbiani here?     - Um, no.
如果你见到他 请转告他我在找他
If you see him, please tell him that I'm looking for him...
这次我不会吐了
and that this time I am not gonna throw up!
- 你还好吗？ - 我？我很好
- Are you okay?     - Me? I'm great!
我很好 我好的不得了
I'm fine! I'm so good.
但是你知道谁不好？
But you know who's not great?
男人
Men!
- 你是男人对吧？罗斯   - 对
- You're a man, right, Ross?     - Yeah.
- 坐下   - 好
- Sit down.     - Okay.
我问你一件事
Let me, uh, ask you something.
婚誓对你们来说是个屁吗？
Do wedding vows mean squat to you people?
为什么我们一说要出门
Why is it that the second we go out of town...
砰 你们就跟邻居的 遛狗小妹上床？
bam, there you are in bed with the neighbor's dog-walker?
我们很抱歉
We're sorry.
我说真的 婚姻的神圣性呢？
No, seriously. Seriously. What has happened to the sanctity of marriage?
- 你昨晚不是跟乔伊在一起？ - 你是侦探吗？
- Didn't you spend last night at Joey's?     - Oh, what are you, a detective?
我不知道你和你丈夫怎么了...
I don't know what's going on with you and your husband...
希望那位遛狗妹已经成年
and what is hopefully an adult dog-walker.
但我要说男人并非都那样
Look, can I just say, not all men are like that.
- 呃   - 有些男人
- Ugh.     - Hey, there are some men...
愿意尽全力挽回婚姻
who'll do whatever to make their marriage work.
有些男人愿意退到一边
There are some men who will stand by and watch...
看老婆跟健身房刚认识的女人
as their wives engage in what can only be described as a "twosome"...
打得火热旁若无人
with some woman she barely knows from the gym!
这些男人是谁？
Who are these men?
就是我认识的一个人
Just men. A guy I know.
你可能要告诉他 听起来他的老婆
Well, you might want to tell him it sounds like his wife...
是同性恋
is gay.
她才不是...
She is not...
她是同性恋
She's gay.
天哪
Oh, my God.
她好同性恋
She is so gay!
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
已婚者的黄道吉日
Good day for married people, huh?
很遗憾你老公不忠
I'm sorry your husband cheated on you.
很遗憾你老婆是同性恋
I'm sorry your wife is gay.
- 看来女人也没那么好   - 去告诉我老婆啊
- I guess women aren't that great either.     - Try telling my wife that.
- 我可以进来吗？ - 进来 吃饭 随你便
- Okay to come in?     - Yeah, come in, eat, whatever you want.
罗杰医生又被叫走了
Dr. Roger got beeped again.
我知道 你猜是谁叫走他的？
Yeah, I know. Guess who beeped him?
- 什么？ - 我就是那个脾脏破裂患者
- What?     - I'm the ruptured spleen. Ha, ha!
- 你为什么要这样？ - 因为你不该和他在起
- Why would you do that?     - Because you shouldn't be with him.
你应该和我在一起
You should be with me.
- 是吗？ - 听你聊罗杰
- Really?     - When you were talking about Roger...
让我好痛苦
that was killing me. Look.
昨晚的事不是说要就要的
Things like last night don't just happen.
至少对我来说不是 跟另外两个女人在一起时...
At least not to me. I mean, with the other two women...
到了早上 我巴不得赶快去找朋友
in the morning, I couldn't wait to just go hang out with my friends.
但是跟你...
But with you...
我就是跟朋友在一起
heh, I was, you know, already with a friend.
- 钱德   - 你八成不想跟我交往
- Chandler.     - You probably don't want to go out with me.
因为我太爱开玩笑 也没认真谈过感情
I make too many jokes, I've never been in a serious relationship...
又不是个"医生"
and I guess I'm not technically a "doctor."
只有一个女人对不对？
There was just one woman, wasn't there?
真的 有两个
No, there were two.
- 一个是我？ - 正是
- Including me?     - Oh, yeah.
两次心脏病发才终于让你认清
It only takes two heart attacks To finally make you see
一次死不了 但第二次会让你解脱
One of them won't do it But the second will set you free
告诉你的恨意与愤怒 是该道别了
Tell all your hate and anger It's time to say goodbye
只要我的老板们一死
And that is just what I will do
我就会这么做
Soon as those bastards I worked for die
啦啦啦 啦啦啦
La, la-la la, la la la la la la La la la, la la la-la-la la